Now that we have our actions, our reducer,
我们已经创建了 action 和 reducer
and we've hooked up redux inter app using provider and create store,
并使用 provider 和 createStore 将 redux 关联到应用中
the next thing we want to do is,
下一步是
actually go ahead and connect our addEntry component.
连接 AddEntry 组件
So that way, we can add some functionality right here,
这样的话 当我们提交新的条目时
when we submit a new entry.
我们可以在这里添加一些功能
And then, we can also add some redux functionality right here,
并且当我们重置某一天的信息时
when we reset the specific day.
可以在这里添加一些 redux 功能
So what we'll do is let's go ahead and import a few things.
我们先导入一些内容
We will import connect which is coming from react-redux.
我们将导入 connect 来自于 react-redux
And then, we are also going to import our addEntry action creator,
然后导入 addEntry action creator
which is coming from our actions file.
来自于 actions 文件
So now, what we can do is instead of exporting the component,
我们不再导出组件
what we want to do,
而是导出
is we want to export the invocation of connect.
对 connect 的调用
And then the result of that,
结果是
we will pass addEntry.
传递 AddEntry
So now, AddEntry is going to have access to dispatch.
现在 AddEntry 将能够访问 dispatch
So what we can do is inside of our submit,
在 submit 中
where it says update redux,
写着更新 redux 的地方
what we're going to do is we'll say, this.props.dispatch.
输入 this.props.dispatch
And what we want to dispatch is what we just barely imported, which was AddEntry.
我们要分派的是刚刚导入的 addEntry
And if you remember what AddEntry accepts is it accepts a new entry.
addEntry 接受的是新的条目
And it's right here, it accepts a new entry.
在这里 它接受的是新的条目
And then eventually, what's going to happen is
最终 该条目
that entry is going to be added to our state.
将被添加到我们的 state 上
So we want to format it like this or we have the key,
输入 key
which is the return value of timeToString.
它是 timeToString 的返回值
And then the value is going to be entry,
value 将是 entry
which is really just our state,
其实就是我们的 state
which has all of these properties on it.
它具有所有这些属性
So now whenever we hit submit,
现在 每当我们点击提交时
not only are we resetting our state and we are updating our database,
我们不仅会重置状态和更新数据库
we're also dispatching our addEntry action creator,
并且会分派 addEntry action creator
which is saving the specific entry to our redux store.
它负责将具体的条目保存到 redux store 中
Now, we can do something really similar down here.
现在 在下面执行非常相似的流程
So this reset function is going to
每当我们点击这里的这个 reset 按钮时
be ran whenever we click on this reset button right here.
这个 reset 函数将会运行
So what we want to do,
现在将和之前一样
just as we did before, we'll say, this.props.dispatch,
输入 this.props.dispatch
what we want to dispatch is addEntry is going to be the exact same.
我们要分派的是 addEntry key 完全一样
But now, instead of being the specific entry,
但现在我们希望将其重置为初始状态
we kind of just want to reset it to what it initially was.
而不是具体的条目
So if we look at our app These are the exact same screens.
看看我们的应用 这些是完全一样的屏幕
Notice over here, this is the current day, August 30.
注意这里是当前日期：8 月 30 日
We're saying don't forget to log your data today.
我们提示别忘了记录今天的数据
And this is different than say August 2,
8 月 2 日不一样
which is just a day that you didn't log any information.
提示你没有记录任何信息
So inside of our redux store,
因此在 redux store 中
we really have three different values.
我们有三种不同的值
We have the value right here, which is an object,
第一种是这里的值 也就是一个对象
which has a run, bike, swim,
包含 run、bike、swim
eat, and sleep property on it.
eat 和 sleep 属性
And the values of those properties are just 30, 65,
这些属性的值为 30、65、5153
5153, basically whatever the values of the specific metric is.
表示具体指标的值
We have this right here,
在这里
the key is going to be August 2,
键将是 2017 年 8 月 2 日
2017 and the value is going to be null.
值将为空
And then over here,
然后在这里
notice that we haven't logged any information but it's today.
注意 我们没有记录任何信息 但日期是今天
We don't just want to say you didn't log any data on this day,
我们不能说没有记录这一天的数据
we actually want to say, hey don't forget to log your data.
我们希望提醒的是：嘿 别忘了记录数据
So what we're going to do here is inside of our helper's file,
转到 helpers 文件
let's create a brand new function.
新建一个函数
We're going to call it,
名称设为
getDailyReminderValue and what it's going to
getDailyReminderValue
do is it's going to return us an object which has a day property.
它将返回一个具有日期属性的对象
And the value is going to be, we'll say,
值将为“挥手”表情符
wave and then we will say,
然后输入文本
don't forget to log your data today.
“Don't forget to log your data today!”
And so now, what we can do is whenever we want to reset the value for the specific day,
现在 每当我们想重置某一天的值时
we can just call this function and we will get this object back.
我们将调用这个函数并获得这个对象
So inside of AddEntry,
转到 AddEntry 文件
let's go ahead and import this.
导入这个组件
It's coming from utils, helpers.
来自于 /utils/helpers
Looks like we already have the import up here so we can
似乎在这里从该路径中导入了内容
add getDailyReminderValue to that.
直接在这里添加 getDailyReminderValue
And then now what we want to do is, again,
在提交数据时
instead of resetting this to the entry as we're doing when we submit it,
我们将此重置为 entry
when we reset it what we want to do is we'll invoke, getDailyReminderValue.
但是当我们重置时 我们将调用 getDailyReminderValue.
So again, that way, whenever a reset runs,
这样的话 每当 reset 运行时
we want to reset the value of this property
我们将 state 上这个属性的值
on our state to be the default value for this specific day,
设为这一天的默认值
which is going to say, hey don't forget to log your information for today.
也就是提示别忘了记录今天的信息
Now the last thing we need to do here is if you'll remember,
最后的任务时 如果还记得的话
we have this section right here which is basically saying, hey,
这一部分的作用是提示：
if you've already logged your information for the day,
如果你已经记录了当天的信息
show this for you instead of letting them re-log their information.
则显示这个视图 而不是让用户重新记录信息
So what we can do is,
现在我们在这里
let's create a function down here,
创建一个函数
we'll call it mapStateToProps and this is going to receive these states.
称为 mapStateToProps 它将接收 state
We can create a brand new key by doing timeToString again, as we've done.
我们可以像之前一样 通过调用 timeToString 创建新的 key
And then, in order for us to know if
为了知道
the user has already logged their information or not,
用户是否已经记录信息
if state[key] which is the key for today is a thing and type
输入 state[key] &amp;&amp; 也就是今天的 key
of state[key].today equals undefined
然后输入 typeof state[key].today === ‘undefined’
and that means they have already logged their information.
表示用户已经记录信息
So again, if state[key] is a thing,
如果 state[key] 具有内容
meaning it's not null,
也就是不为空
and state[key].today is undefined and the reason we have this line right here is because,
并且 state[key].today 为 undefined 这行的作用是
going back to this,
回到应用界面
this section down here is going to be an object with all these properties.
这部分将是一个具有所有这些属性的对象
This section is going to be null.
这部分将为空
But this section is going to have a today property just as we're doing right here.
但是这部分将具有 today 属性 正如这行代码所表示的
So we're saying, if the value at a specific date in our redux store has a today property,
如果特定日期的值在 redux store 中具有 today 属性
then that means they haven't already logged their information.
则表示用户尚未记录信息
So then, this.props.alreadyLogged will be false.
this.props.alreadyLogged 将为 false
Let me go ahead and fix this formatting.
我调整下格式
And then, now, we want to pass napStateToProps to our connect function.
现在向 connect 函数传入 mapStateToProps
And I just spotted this typo,
发现了个拼写错误
we don't want to export connect,
应该输入 export default connect
we want to export default connect.
而不是 export connect
And then now, our app should still be running.
现在我们的应用应该依然能运行
We can actually just go ahead and test list.
我们可以测试下
Let's try to go ahead and submit one of these,
尝试调整这些信息并提交
simplest two, four. So we submit it.
将这个设成 4 并提交
Notice that we get the screen because
注意 出现了这个屏幕
alreadyLogged was passed to our component as true, right here.
因为在这里 alreadyLogged 被传入组件并且为 true
And then, we should be able to reset this,
我们应该能够在这里进行重置
which then takes us back to the screen right here.
回到这个屏幕